<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cool on William Bradshaw</title>
    <link>https://will.forsale/tags/cool/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cool on William Bradshaw</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 12:56:48 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://will.forsale/tags/cool/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pizza is the best food ever and here is why. Can you tell I like it?</title>
      <link>https://will.forsale/blog/pizzaisawesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 12:56:48 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://will.forsale/blog/pizzaisawesome/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo! JAPAN is one of the largest media companies in Japan, providing services such as search, news, e-commerce, and e-mail. Over 50 million users log in to Yahoo! JAPAN services every month.
Over the years, there were many attacks on user accounts and issues that led to lost account access. Most of these issues were related to password usage for authentication.
With recent advances in authentication technology, Yahoo! JAPAN has decided to move from password-based to passwordless authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo! JAPAN&#39;s password-free authentication reduced inquiries by 25%, sped up sign-in time by 2.6</title>
      <link>https://will.forsale/blog/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 12:54:48 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://will.forsale/blog/example/</guid>
      <description>This is Markdown The best thing ever to exist ever
Overview Philosophy Markdown is intended to be as easy-to-read and easy-to-write as is feasible.
Readability, however, is emphasized above all else. A Markdown-formatted document should be publishable as-is, as plain text, without looking like it&amp;rsquo;s been marked up with tags or formatting instructions. While Markdown&amp;rsquo;s syntax has been influenced by several existing text-to-HTML filters &amp;ndash; including Setext, atx, Textile, reStructuredText, Grutatext, and EtText &amp;ndash; the single biggest source of inspiration for Markdown&amp;rsquo;s syntax is the format of plain text email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
